<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spirituality on BlogHunt</title>
    <link>https://blogworld2.netlify.app/categories/spirituality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spirituality on BlogHunt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 21:53:32 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blogworld2.netlify.app/categories/spirituality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Affirations</title>
      <link>https://blogworld2.netlify.app/posts/spiritual/affirations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 21:53:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blogworld2.netlify.app/posts/spiritual/affirations/</guid>
      <description>Unlock Your Inner Fire: 9 Power-Packed Affirmations from Spiritual Giants Ever feel like life’s throwing punches and you’re just dodging? These affirmations from Swami Vivekananda and Swami Paramahansa Yogananda—two legends who lit up the world with wisdom—are your knockout blows to self-doubt. They’re not just words; they’re sparks to set your soul ablaze. Ready to rise, shine, and conquer? Let’s dive into these game-changers!
Affirmations That’ll Transform You Self-Confidence and Perseverance Affirmation: &amp;ldquo;I arise, awake, and will not stop until my goal is reached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autobiography of a Yogi</title>
      <link>https://blogworld2.netlify.app/posts/spiritual/jay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 21:53:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blogworld2.netlify.app/posts/spiritual/jay/</guid>
      <description>Summary The book is a spiritual autobiography of Paramahansa Yogananda, who is credited with introducing yoga and meditation to the West in the 1920s. The book begins with his childhood family life, to finding his guru, to becoming a monk and establishing his teachings of Kriya Yoga meditation. The book continues in 1920 when Yogananda accepts an invitation to speak in a religious congress in Boston, Massachusetts, USA. He then travels across America lecturing and establishing his teachings in Los Angeles, California.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
